{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"3826","name":"Domino's Pizza","address":"5564 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Aaron Dolkowski","licenseNumber":"200066","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","coords":"-83.06725,42.36139","geojson":{"id":"3826","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.067251098,42.3613923180001]},"properties":{"name":"Domino's Pizza","owner":"Aaron Dolkowski","address":"5564 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"200066","establishmentid":"3826","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/9/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3707","name":"Wasabi","address":"15 E Kirby St","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"4370","name":"Fourteen East, LLC","address":"15 E Kirby St., Suite 113","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"4854","name":"The Detroit Pizza Co. /Nom Nom's Cupcake","address":"15 E Kirby St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"51622667","name":"Park Shelton Pizza","address":"15 E Kirby St., Suite 115","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"5011","name":"Chartreuse Kitchen & Cocktails","address":"15 E Kirby St., Suite D","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"5431","name":"Common Pub","address":"5440 Cass Ave ","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"1440","name":"Campus Diner","address":"5470 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"591","name":"Byblos Cafe & Grill","address":"87 W Palmer Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"51622915","name":"College for Creative Studies","address":"201 Kirby St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"573","name":"Circa 1890 Saloon","address":"5474 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48202"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"42581","inspectionDate":"2018-06-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"41009","inspectionDate":"2017-12-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"In the Cold table","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"ceiling","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"and the Knives","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"and the PERSON IN CHARGE","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"In the Facility","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"}]},{"inspectionid":"40827","inspectionDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-201.11","violationDescription":"The PERMIT HOLDER shall require FOOD EMPLOYEE applicants and  FOOD EMPLOYEES to report to the PERSON IN CHARGE,  information about their health and activities as they relate to diseases that are transmissible through FOOD. AND report the information in a manner that allows the PERSON IN CHARGE to prevent the likelihood of foodborne disease transmission.(P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Fail to require employees to report illness as rule requires","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Require reporting as stated above."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"PIZZA PREP AREA","subLocation":"Cooler (pizza-prep)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"PIZZA PREP AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"violationCode":"2-201.12","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall:  Exclude or restrict employees with symptom of illness or past illness as required by the code.(P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Failed to restrict sick/ill employee(s)","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Place restrictions as required by code."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"PIZZA PREP AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"37454","inspectionDate":"2016-12-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2019-05-31T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"3826"}}